Guide to the Exiles Film Project records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Interviews, Series II
  - Zimmer, Christiane
    - Zimmer, Christiane, 1988 January 21; 16; 1.0 (Box 274)
    - Zimmer, Christaine dub, Circa 1980s; 15A; 1.0 (Box 275)
    - Zimmer, Christaine dub, Circa 1980s; 16; 1.0 (Box 276)
- Kine sync reels, Series III
  - K-1: Bettelheim, Kellen, Lerner, Eisenstaedt, Hirschmann, Zimmer, Lowe; Assimilation; Code BA0000 (Box 277)
    - Kine R-1, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-1, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-1, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-1, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-2: Lowenthal, Golo Mann, Nono, Waldo, Roth, Teller; Assimilation; Code BA3000 (Box 278)
    - Kine R-2, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-2, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BA 3000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BA 3001, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-3 (1): Speier, Golo Mann, Helen Wolff, Seltz; Assimilation; Code BA6000 (Box 279)
    - Kine R-3, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-3, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-3 BA 6000-8000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-3 BA 6000-8000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-3 (2): Kline Interview; Code BA7000 (Box 280)
    - Wolf BA 7000 (K-3 Interview), Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Wolf BA 7000 (K-3 Interview), Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Wolf BA 7000 (K-3 Interview), Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-4: Hirschman, Nono, Jonas; German American Academe, German Anti-Semitism, Reaction of intellectuals to the Nazis; Code BB0000 (Box 281)
    - Kine R-4, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-4, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-4 BB 0000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-4 BB 0000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-5: Bettelhaim, Jonas, Lowe, Eisenstadt, Hirschman, Speier, Wolf, Seltz; Rise of the Nazis; Code BB3000 (Box 282)
    - Kine R-5, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-5, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-5 BB 3000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-6: Bettelheim, Golo Mann, Lowe, Roth, Seltz; US immigration policies; Code BB6000 (Box 283)
  - Kine R-6, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-6, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-5 BB 3000-3999, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-5 BB 3000-4000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Hanmabrey Ron, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-5 cont. BB 4000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-5 cont. BB 4000 (cont.), Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BB 6000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BB 6000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-7: Jonas, Hughes, Regfield, Wolf; Arendt; Code BC0000 (Box 284)
    - Kine R-7, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-7, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-8: Roth, Eisenstaedt; Brecht, Eisenstaedt in America; Code BC3000 (Box 285)
    - Kine R-8, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-8, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-9 (1): Frankfurt School, Hannah Gray; Code BC6000 (Box 286)
    - Kine R-9, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-9, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-9 (2): Frankfurt School, Hannah Gray; Code BC3000 (Box 287)
    - K-9 BC 6000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-9 BC 6001, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-9 BC 6002, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-9 BC 6003, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-10: Hajo Holborn, Impact; Code BD0000 (Box 288)
    - Kine R-10, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-10, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-11: Impact continued, Jonas view; Code BD3000 (Box 289)
    - Kine R-11, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-12, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-12: Lowe's work; Code BD6000 (Box 290)
    - Kine R-12 (Lowe's work), Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-12, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-13 (1): Marcuse; McCarthy period; Code BE0000 (Box 291)
    - Kine R-13 (Marcuse-McCarthy period), Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-13, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-13 BE 0000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-13 (2): McCarthy (Box 292)
    - BE 0000 Lowe - Lowenthal - McCarthyism, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Lowe - Lowenthal - McCarthyism, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-14: Music; Code BE3000 (Box 293)
    - Kine R-14 (Music), Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-14, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-14 BE 3000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-15: Piscator; Code BE6000 (Box 294)
    - Kine R-15 (Piscator), Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-15, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-16 (1): Physicists, Psychonalalysis; Code BG0000 (Box 295)
    - Kine R-16, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-16, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-16 (2): Code BG0000 (Box 296)
    - Film Witness, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-16 BG 0000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BG 2000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-16 BG 0000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-17: Leo Strauss, Student revolt; Code BG3000 (Box 297)
    - Kine R-17 (Leo Strauss), Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-17, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-17 BG 3000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-18: War effort; Code BG6000 (Box 298)
    - Kine R-18 (Warehort), Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-18, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-18 BG 6000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-19 (1): Writers; Code BH0000 (Box 299)
    - Kine R-19 (Writers), Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-19, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BH 0000 Pix/trk, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-19 (2): Code BH0000 (Box 300)
    - Assembly Part II California (Mann), Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BH 0000 Assembly California (Thomas Mann) Part II, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-20: Writers, 1960s, Art History, Bauhaus; Code BH3000 (Box 301)
    - Kine R-20 (Bauhaus-Writers 1960's Art History), Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-20, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BH 3000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BH 3001, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BH 3002, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-21: Literature; Code BH6000 (Box 302)
    - Kine R-21 (Literature), Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-21, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-22: Non-interviews; Code BJ0000 (Box 303)
    - Kine R-22 (non-interview), Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-22, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-23: Non-interviews, room tone; Code BJ3000 (Box 304)
    - Kine R-23 (non-interview room tone), Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-23, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-24: Code BJ6000 (Box 305)
    - Kine R-24, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-24, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-24 BJ 6000-6999, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-24 BJ 6000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BJ 7000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BJ 6000 pix+trk, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BJ 7000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-25: Code BK0000 (Box 306)
    - Kine R-25, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-26, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-25, K-26: Codes BK0000, BK3000 (Box 307)
    - K-25 BK 0000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-25 BK 0000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-26: Code BK 3000 (Box 308)
    - K-26 BK 3000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BK 3000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BK 3000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-26 BK 3000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-26 BK 3000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BK 3000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BK 3000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-27: Code BK6000 (Box 309)
    - Kine R-27 BK 6000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-27 BK 6000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BK 6000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BK 6000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-28: U in E; Code BL0000 (Box 310)
    - Kine R-28 BL 0000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-28 BL 0000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BL 0000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BL 0000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-29: U in E, R.T /0; Code BL3000 (Box 311)
    - K-28 BL 0000-1499, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-28 BL 1500-3999, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-29 BL 3000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-29 BL 3000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-28 BL 1500-3999, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - K-28 BL 0000-1499, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-30: U in E/Theatre R.T.; Code BL6000 (Box 312)
    - Kine R-30 BL 6000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Kine R-30 BL 6000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-31: ERC; Code BM0000 (Box 313)
    - BM 0000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BM 0000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BM 0000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-32: ERC, U in E; Code BM3000 (Box 314)
    - BM 3000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BM 3000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BM 3000-3999, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BM 4000-5999, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BM 3278, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BM 3000-3999, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-34: Book Burning; Code BN0000 (Box 315)
    - BN 0000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BN 0000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BN 0000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BN 0000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-35, K-36: Codes BN3000, BN6000 (Box 316)
    - BN 6000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BN 3000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BN 6000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BN 3000 R-35, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BN 6294 Salvador, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BN 6000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BN 6000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BN 3000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BN 3000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BN 3000 Johnson Redo, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BN 3000 Johnson Redo, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BN 3000 R-35, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-37 (1): Code BP0000 (Box 317)
    - BP 0000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BP 0000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-37 (2): Code BP0000 (Box 318)
    - BP 0000, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BN 3379, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Golo Mann, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Golo Mann, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - K-37 (3): Code BP0000 (Box 319)
    - Redfield on Are, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Redfield on Arendt, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - Untitled, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - SR-29, Dichter interview; Code BQ0000 (Box 320)
    - BQ 0000 Dichter outs, Circa 1980s; 1.0
    - BQ 0000 Dichter outs, Circa 1980s; 1.0
  - University in Exile Promo
    - University in Exile Promo (Time 10:00), 1988 September 9; 1.0 (Box 321)
    - University in Exile Promo (Time 12:00), 1988 October 24; 1.0 (Box 322)
    - University in Exile Promo (Time 12:00), 1988 September 9; 1.0 (Box 323)
    - University in Exile Promo (Time 1:33), 1988 October 24; 1.0 (Box 324)
    - University in Exile Promo (Time 5:10), 1988 October 25; 1.0 (Box 325)
    - University in Exile Promo (Time 5:00), 1988 November 9; 1.0 (Box 326)
  - Exiles hour 2, reel 1, dial A, Circa 1980s; 1.0 (Box 327)
  - Exiles hour 2, reel 1, dial B, Circa 1980s; 1.0 (Box 328)
  - Exiles hour 2, reel 2, dial A and B, Circa 1980s; 1.0 (Box 329)
  - Original negative assembled roll 29, Rolls 1, 2, 3, 1988 May 16; 1.0 (Box 330)
  - Original negative assembled roll 30, Roll X, 1988 May 16; 1.0 (Box 331)
  - Original negative assembled roll 38, Rolls 13-16, 1988 June 9; 1.0 (Box 332)
  - Original negative assembled roll 39, Rolls 17-19, 1988 June 9; 1.0 (Box 333)
  - Stills Rolls 11-12, Circa 1980s; 1.0 (Box 334)
  - Stills Roll 15, 1988 November 28; 1.0 (Box 335)
  - Assembled Roll 13, 1988 March 18; 1.0 (Box 336)
  - Assembled Roll: Rolls 1-4, 1988 March 18; 1.0 (Box 337)
  - Assembled Roll 46, Circa 1980s; 1.0 (Box 338)
  - Assembled Roll 47, Circa 1980s; 1.0 (Box 339)
  - Assembled Roll 48, 1988 November 1; 1.0 (Box 340)
  - Assembled Roll 49, Circa 1980s; 1.0 (Box 341)
  - Assembled Roll 53, 1988 November 11; 1.0 (Box 342)
  - Assembled Roll 54, 1988 November 14; 1.0 (Box 343)
  - Assembled Roll 55, 1988 November 30; 1.0 (Box 344)
  - Assembled Roll 59, 1988 November 8; 1.0 (Box 345)
  - Assembled Roll 60, 1988 November 7; 1.0 (Box 346)
  - Assembled Roll 63, Circa 1980s; 1.0 (Box 347)
  - Assembled Roll 5, 1988 May 31; 1.0 (Box 348)
  - Assembled Roll 6, 1988 May 31; 1.0 (Box 349)
  - Assembled Roll 19, 1988 June 20; 1.0 (Box 350)
  - Assembled Roll 33, 1988 June 20; 1.0 (Box 351)
- Production records, Series IV
  - Scripts and narration, 1989 March 10 (Box 352, Folder 1)
  - Video excerpt log and Kine selects log, 1988 March 14 (Box 352, Folder 2)
  - Rerecording cue sheet, Circa 1980s (Box 353, Folder 1)
  - Reel list, Circa 1980s (Box 353, Folder 2)